<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<PedAnswers>
  <!-- Drinking -->
  <Drinking question="~g~Have you been drinking?">
    <Positive>
      <Answer>I had a few shots of tequila at the Bahama Mamas, just to unwind.</Answer>
      <Answer>I drank a six-pack of beer from the 24/7 on Elgin Avenue, but I’m fine.</Answer>
      <Answer>Yes, I had a couple of beers at the Yellow Jack Inn in Sandy Shores.</Answer>
      <Answer>Yes, I sipped some wine at the Vangelico Casino in Vinewood, nothing serious.</Answer>
      <Answer>Of course, I had a drink to unwind from a day at Los Santos Customs. It’s been a rough day.</Answer>
      <Answer>Booze warms me up after a long shift at the Maze Bank; it’s cold out there.</Answer>
      <Answer>Alcoholic drinks are my favorite after a night at the Vanilla Unicorn; helps me relax.</Answer>
      <Answer>I need a drink to stay focused, like a bourbon from the Boathouse; helps me clear my head.</Answer>
      <Answer>I had a drink at the Tinsel Towers Rooftop Bar to enjoy the view.</Answer>
      <Answer>I was drinking at the LSC in Strawberry, but I’m not drunk, just tired.</Answer>
      <Answer>I had some moonshine at the Blaine County trailer park, but it’s nothing to worry about.</Answer>
      <Answer>I had a nightcap at the Los Santos Golf Club, just to finish off the evening.</Answer>
      <Answer>Had a few brews at the Happy Vixen in Paleto Bay; it was a long day.</Answer>
      <Answer>I had a drink at the Del Perro Pier, enjoying the seaside.</Answer>
      <Answer>I was drinking at the O’Neil Ranch; nothing too wild, just a quiet evening.</Answer>
      <Answer>Last stop was the Clubhouse in Mirror Park; just a casual night out.</Answer>
      <Answer>I just finished a few drinks at the Paleto Bay Saloon; it’s been a long day.</Answer>
      <Answer>Had some cocktails at the Vespucci Beach Boardwalk, trying to unwind.</Answer>
      <Answer>Drank at the Eclipse Tower’s penthouse party, just a few to celebrate.</Answer>
      <Answer>Had a few beers at the Vinewood Bowl after the show, relaxing with friends.</Answer>
    </Positive>
    <Negative>
      <Answer>I don't drink alcohol; it's not my thing. I prefer staying clear-headed.</Answer>
      <Answer>Alcohol is not part of my lifestyle; I prefer a latte from the Bean Machine, keeps me alert.</Answer>
      <Answer>I've never had a drink in my life; I'm always sober and focused.</Answer>
      <Answer>I’m as sharp as an eagle; no alcohol here. I keep my mind clear for work.</Answer>
      <Answer>No, I haven't had anything to drink today. Just heading to work.</Answer>
      <Answer>I've been sober for 6 months, focused on work at the Los Santos Auto Showroom; I’m turning my life around.</Answer>
      <Answer>Do you smell alcohol on me? I was just at the Prawn Shack in Paleto Bay for a meal.</Answer>
      <Answer>Nope, I don’t drink at all. I stay away from it to maintain my health.</Answer>
      <Answer>Alcohol isn't for me; I prefer a clear mind for work at the Pacific Standard.</Answer>
      <Answer>No drinks; I’m strictly business, like my job at the Blaine County Sheriff’s Office.</Answer>
    </Negative>
  </Drinking>
  
  <!-- Drugs -->
  <Drugs question="~o~Have you done any drugs recently?">
    <Positive>
      <Answer>I use prescription pills for a condition; I got them from the Pillbox Medical. They’re legal.</Answer>
      <Answer>I take some medication for my health, prescribed by my doctor at the hospital.</Answer>
      <Answer>Sometimes I use drugs for pleasure, like what you might find at a local rave in Vinewood, but it’s under control.</Answer>
      <Answer>I use drugs from time to time; they’re obtained from a trusted source in the city, nothing excessive.</Answer>
      <Answer>Drugs can be part of wellness if used responsibly; I get mine from Sandy Shores Medical Center.</Answer>
      <Answer>I’m feeling high now; just came from a party at Los Santos Customs. But it’s nothing to worry about.</Answer>
      <Answer>Do I need to answer that? My doctor at the Sandy Shores Medical knows about my medication.</Answer>
      <Answer>I have the right to remain silent about my personal habits.</Answer>
      <Answer>Used some recreational drugs at the Hippie Camp near Mount Chiliad; it’s a part of my lifestyle.</Answer>
      <Answer>Had a dose from a dealer at the Redwood Lights Track; it’s for personal use.</Answer>
      <Answer>Taking prescribed meds for anxiety from the Harmony Medical Center; they help me manage stress.</Answer>
    </Positive>
    <Negative>
      <Answer>No drugs; they make you sick and aren't worth it. I prefer staying healthy.</Answer>
      <Answer>Why would I use drugs? I prefer a healthy life, like my role at the Los Santos Police Department.</Answer>
      <Answer>I’ve never used drugs; my lifestyle is clean, working at the Paleto Bay Sheriff’s Station.</Answer>
      <Answer>Do I look like a drug addict? I’m just a regular person from Grove Street.</Answer>
      <Answer>I've been clean for a year; my focus is on work at the Los Santos Auto Showroom.</Answer>
      <Answer>Nope, no drugs here. I stay far away from them.</Answer>
      <Answer>No money, no drugs; just a normal life in the city.</Answer>
      <Answer>Never touched drugs; I work at the Vinewood TV Station and stay clean.</Answer>
    </Negative>
  </Drugs>
  
  <!-- Illegal Items -->
  <IllegalItem question="~r~Do you have anything illegal on you?">
    <Answer>No sir, I’m just an ordinary citizen. I keep everything above board.</Answer>
    <Answer>I’m a good citizen, no illegal items here. Everything I have is legal.</Answer>
    <Answer>I don’t want to go to jail; I keep everything above board, nothing illegal.</Answer>
    <Answer>Perhaps I have something, but it’s not my intention to hide anything. I’m open to a search.</Answer>
    <Answer>I’m not sure; check for yourself, but I doubt it. Everything I carry is legal.</Answer>
    <Answer>Nope, nothing illegal on me. I keep my belongings in order.</Answer>
    <Answer>I completely forgot; my mind is preoccupied with work at the Maze Bank.</Answer>
    <Answer>You don’t have the right to search me without cause; I know my rights.</Answer>
    <Answer>Maybe yes, maybe no; I don’t remember. But I assure you, nothing illegal.</Answer>
    <Answer>I'm clean; all my stuff is legal. I’m just heading to the beach for a break.</Answer>
    <Answer>I keep my belongings in order, no illegal stuff here. Everything is as it should be.</Answer>
    <Answer>Only legal items; I work at the Los Santos Police Department.</Answer>
    <Answer>No contraband; I'm just heading to the beach for a break. Everything is in order.</Answer>
    <Answer>Nothing here but my work tools from the Los Santos Customs. Everything is legal.</Answer>
  </IllegalItem>
  
  <!-- What Are You Doing -->
  <PedDoing question="~g~What are you doing?">
    <Answer>Just hanging around, enjoying the view from the Rockford Hills. It’s been a nice day.</Answer>
    <Answer>I need some fresh air after a long day at the Maze Bank. A bit of relaxation.</Answer>
    <Answer>I’m relaxing my soul, taking it easy at the Vinewood Hills. Enjoying the peaceful surroundings.</Answer>
    <Answer>I’m waiting for a friend to meet me at the Prawn Shack in Paleto Bay. It’s a chill spot.</Answer>
    <Answer>It's none of your business; I’m simply out for a stroll. Enjoying the day.</Answer>
    <Answer>Please mind your own business; I’m just visiting the Los Santos Customs. Nothing suspicious.</Answer>
    <Answer>Why do you care? I’m just passing time in the Grove Street area. It’s a normal day for me.</Answer>
    <Answer>I choose not to answer; it’s a private matter. My business is my own.</Answer>
    <Answer>I have the right to remain silent; I’m not obligated to explain my whereabouts.</Answer>
    <Answer>Just finishing up some errands; I was at the 24/7 store. Running my daily tasks.</Answer>
    <Answer>Running some personal errands before heading to the Vinewood Bowl. It’s been a busy day.</Answer>
    <Answer>Waiting for a ride from the Yellow Jack Inn. Just wrapping up a visit.</Answer>
    <Answer>Just enjoying the day at the Del Perro Pier. It’s a nice place to relax.</Answer>
    <Answer>Chilling at the Harmony Medical Center, nothing much. Just taking a break.</Answer>
    <Answer>On a break from work; grabbed a coffee from the Bean Machine. A quick pit stop.</Answer>
  </PedDoing>
  
  <!-- Where Did You Come From -->
  <PedFrom question="~b~Where did you come from?">
    <Answer>From my apartment in Los Santos. Just out for a bit of fresh air.</Answer>
    <Answer>From my friend’s place in Vinewood. We had a good time catching up.</Answer>
    <Answer>From work at the Los Santos Auto Showroom. Just finished up for the day.</Answer>
    <Answer>From the grocery store at the 24/7. Picking up some essentials.</Answer>
    <Answer>From the hospital; I just had a check-up at the Pillbox Medical. Everything is fine.</Answer>
    <Answer>I came from the bar at the Bahama Mamas. Had a couple of drinks.</Answer>
    <Answer>I have the right not to answer; it’s personal. My whereabouts are my own concern.</Answer>
    <Answer>I have the right to remain silent; my origins are my own business. Nothing to report.</Answer>
    <Answer>Just left the Sandy Shores Medical Center. Had a routine visit.</Answer>
    <Answer>From the Blaine County Sheriff’s Office. Just wrapped up some paperwork.</Answer>
    <Answer>Came from the Los Santos Golf Club. Had a round of golf with some friends.</Answer>
    <Answer>I was at the Rockford Hills apartment complex. Just stepping out for a bit.</Answer>
    <Answer>Just came from a meeting at the Los Santos International Airport. It was productive.</Answer>
  </PedFrom>
  
  <!-- Where Are You Headed -->
  <PedTo question="~y~Where are you headed to?">
    <Answer>I’m on my way home to my apartment in Rockford Hills. Just heading back.</Answer>
    <Answer>Just heading to work at the Los Santos Customs. Got some tasks to complete.</Answer>
    <Answer>Going to the grocery store at the 24/7. Need to pick up some things.</Answer>
    <Answer>I’m going to see a friend at the Prawn Shack. Meeting up for some downtime.</Answer>
    <Answer>On my way to the Maze Bank for a meeting. Got some business to handle.</Answer>
    <Answer>Heading to my friend’s place in Grove Street. Just a casual visit.</Answer>
    <Answer>Anywhere I like; it’s a free city. I’m enjoying the day.</Answer>
    <Answer>You don’t need to know; it’s not your concern. My destination is personal.</Answer>
    <Answer>I have the right not to answer; my destination is private. It’s my choice.</Answer>
    <Answer>Off to the Vinewood Bowl for an event. Looking forward to it.</Answer>
    <Answer>Heading to the Del Perro Pier to unwind. It’s a great spot to relax.</Answer>
    <Answer>Going to the Los Santos Golf Club for a round. Just some leisure time.</Answer>
    <Answer>On my way to the O’Neil Ranch to check on some business. Got some work to do.</Answer>
    <Answer>Heading out to the Sandy Shores Airfield. Have a few things to take care of.</Answer>
    <Answer>Off to the Paleto Bay Saloon for a meeting. It’s an important discussion.</Answer>
    <Answer>Going to visit a contact at the Harmony Medical Center. A quick visit.</Answer>
  </PedTo>
</PedAnswers>
