<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<TrafficStopQuestions>
  <TrafficStopQuestion>
    <Question style="color: #ff0000;">Have you been drinking?</Question>
    <Answers>
      <Answer>Just a beer or two from The Pink Cage</Answer>
      <Answer>I had a glass of whiskey from the local bar</Answer>
      <Answer>Yes, a few cocktails at Tequila La La</Answer>
      <Answer>Yes, I had a couple of shots at a party at Eclipse Towers</Answer>
      <Answer>Just a little at the Vinewood Club</Answer>
      <Answer>Had some drinks at the Boilingbroke Penitentiary’s bar</Answer>
      <Answer>I enjoy a drink at The Vanilla Unicorn</Answer>
      <Answer>Just enough to take the edge off from the Alhambra</Answer>
      <Answer>I have the right to remain silent</Answer>
      <Answer>No, I don’t drink</Answer>
      <Answer>I’m not a fan of alcohol</Answer>
      <Answer>Never had a drink; always sober</Answer>
      <Answer>No, I haven’t had any alcohol today</Answer>
      <Answer>I’ve been clean for quite some time</Answer>
    </Answers>
  </TrafficStopQuestion>
  
  <TrafficStopQuestion>
    <Question style="color: #00ff00;">Have you done any drugs recently?</Question>
    <Answers>
      <Answer>I use medication from Pillbox Hill Medical Center</Answer>
      <Answer>I have prescription drugs from Los Santos Custom Pharmacy</Answer>
      <Answer>I use recreational drugs occasionally from the Vespucci Beach scene</Answer>
      <Answer>Sometimes, but it’s under control from the area around San Andreas State</Answer>
      <Answer>Drugs can be helpful in moderation, as seen in GTA 5</Answer>
      <Answer>I’m currently high; does it matter?</Answer>
      <Answer>Is it necessary to answer that?</Answer>
      <Answer>I have the right to remain silent</Answer>
      <Answer>I don’t use drugs; they’re harmful</Answer>
      <Answer>I have no interest in drugs at all</Answer>
      <Answer>Do I look like a drug user to you?</Answer>
      <Answer>I’ve been drug-free for a year now</Answer>
      <Answer>No drugs here!</Answer>
    </Answers>
  </TrafficStopQuestion>
  
  <TrafficStopQuestion>
    <Question style="color: #0000ff;">Where did you come from?</Question>
    <Answers>
      <Answer>Just came from my apartment at Grove Street</Answer>
      <Answer>I was at a friend's place at the Richman area</Answer>
      <Answer>Left work at the Lifeinvader building</Answer>
      <Answer>I was at the grocery store in Del Perro</Answer>
      <Answer>From a meeting at the Maze Bank</Answer>
      <Answer>Just came from a visit at the Los Santos Zoo</Answer>
      <Answer>I was at the Blaine County Sheriff’s Office</Answer>
      <Answer>From the Los Santos International Airport</Answer>
      <Answer>Just left the Vinewood Bowl</Answer>
      <Answer>I came from the Weazel News studio</Answer>
      <Answer>I was at a movie at the Del Perro Pier</Answer>
      <Answer>Visited a friend at the Forum Drive area</Answer>
    </Answers>
  </TrafficStopQuestion>
  
  <TrafficStopQuestion>
    <Question style="color: #ffff00;">Where are you headed to?</Question>
    <Answers>
      <Answer>Heading home to my place in Grove Street</Answer>
      <Answer>On my way to work at the Lifeinvader building</Answer>
      <Answer>Going to the grocery store in Del Perro</Answer>
      <Answer>Off to the airport for a flight</Answer>
      <Answer>Heading to the hospital at Pillbox Hill</Answer>
      <Answer>Going to a meeting at the Maze Bank</Answer>
      <Answer>On my way to the Vinewood Bowl</Answer>
      <Answer>Going to the beach at Vespucci</Answer>
      <Answer>Headed to a party at Eclipse Towers</Answer>
      <Answer>Visiting a friend in the Richman area</Answer>
      <Answer>Going to a concert at the Los Santos Arena</Answer>
    </Answers>
  </TrafficStopQuestion>

  <TrafficStopQuestionGroup name="Violations Operation">
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question style="color: #ff6347;">Why did you run a red light?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>It was a split-second decision at the intersection near Rockford Hills</Answer>
        <Answer>I was rushing to get to the Pacific Standard Bank</Answer>
        <Answer>Thought it was still green at the Vinewood intersection</Answer>
        <Answer>Traffic was clear; didn’t see the harm at the La Mesa intersection</Answer>
        <Answer>Wasn’t paying close attention at the Little Seoul crossing</Answer>
        <Answer>Had to catch the last show at the Del Perro Cinema</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question style="color: #ff4500;">Why didn’t you use your turn signal?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I didn’t think it was necessary at the downtown area</Answer>
        <Answer>Just forgot; it’s not a big deal at the Los Santos freeway</Answer>
        <Answer>Only use it when it’s absolutely needed at the highway</Answer>
        <Answer>It’s not always convenient at the intersection near Los Santos Customs</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question style="color: #ffd700;">Why didn’t you stop at that stop sign?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I didn’t see any other vehicles at the junction near Grove Street</Answer>
        <Answer>Thought it was unnecessary at the intersection by the Vinewood sign</Answer>
        <Answer>Didn’t think it was a critical stop at the corner near the casino</Answer>
        <Answer>It didn’t seem like a major issue at the crossroad near the airport</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question style="color: #dda0dd;">Why were you speeding?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I tend to drive fast on the highways near the Maze Bank</Answer>
        <Answer>I wasn’t aware of the limit at the Vinewood Boulevard</Answer>
        <Answer>Everyone else was speeding too on the Los Santos freeway</Answer>
        <Answer>Was in a hurry for an important meeting at the Lifeinvader building</Answer>
        <Answer>It’s my usual driving style around the city</Answer>
        <Answer>Had to make it to the last appointment at the hospital</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question style="color: #adff2f;">Why were you texting while driving?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Needed to send an urgent message to a client at the Bank of Liberty</Answer>
        <Answer>I thought it was safe at the time on the downtown road</Answer>
        <Answer>My phone is very distracting at the Grove Street area</Answer>
        <Answer>I didn’t realize it was an issue at the intersection near the police station</Answer>
        <Answer>Was coordinating a meetup at the Del Perro Pier</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question style="color: #ff69b4;">Why were you on the phone while driving?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>Had an important call from work at the Maze Bank</Answer>
        <Answer>I was using hands-free in my OPP vehicle</Answer>
        <Answer>My car doesn’t support call assistance from the dealership</Answer>
        <Answer>Didn’t think it would be a problem at the Los Santos freeway</Answer>
        <Answer>Trying to reach a contact at the Weazel News</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question style="color: #ff1493;">Why were you driving recklessly?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I was rushing to the hospital at Pillbox Hill</Answer>
        <Answer>It’s just my usual driving style in the city</Answer>
        <Answer>Apologies, still learning to drive around Los Santos</Answer>
        <Answer>Had an urgent reason for speeding to the Vinewood Bowl</Answer>
        <Answer>Was trying to avoid traffic on the freeway</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question style="color: #8a2be2;">Why were you riding a bike without a helmet?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>It’s too hot to wear one at the Vespucci Beach</Answer>
        <Answer>Can’t afford one right now at the Grove Street area</Answer>
        <Answer>Didn’t want to mess up my hair going to the Los Santos International Airport</Answer>
        <Answer>Forgot it at home near the Richman area</Answer>
        <Answer>Didn’t see it as a big deal at the San Andreas state</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
    
    <TrafficStopQuestion>
      <Question style="color: #00bfff;">Why were you not wearing your seatbelt?</Question>
      <Answers>
        <Answer>I didn’t feel it was necessary for the short drive at the San Andreas freeway</Answer>
        <Answer>It’s uncomfortable on long trips at the Los Santos freeway</Answer>
        <Answer>Had some issues with it; planning to get it fixed</Answer>
        <Answer>Usually don’t wear it in low-speed areas</Answer>
      </Answers>
    </TrafficStopQuestion>
  </TrafficStopQuestionGroup>
</TrafficStopQuestions>
